<patients>
<patient_info>
   <name>Lexidamise</name>
   <age>1</age>
   <location>Haiti</location>
   <partner>Y5GlFHGFuO</partner>
   <donors>12</donors>
   <fund_percent>75</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2078/profile_Lexi_Moliere_D_Haiti_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/7e62b34dc0cc-lexidamise</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Lexidamise is a one-year-old little girl from Haiti. Laxidamise was born with the duo of cleft lip and palate, birth defects that occur when a baby’s lip and mouth do not form properly during pregnancy.

<p>A few months ago, Lexidamise received surgery to repair her lip. Now she needs one more procedure to fix her palate so she can learn to eat like other kids her age. Lexidamise’s mother explains how it is difficult to find anyone who can feed and take care of her child in the special way she needs. As a result, she has been unable to work and cannot afford treatment for Lexidamise.

<p>For $960, Lexidamise will receive surgery to repair her palate and complete the last stage of her treatment. Let’s make sure this little girl grows up healthy and strong!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>240</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Davidson</name>
   <age>2</age>
   <location>Haiti</location>
   <partner>Y5GlFHGFuO</partner>
   <donors>6</donors>
   <fund_percent>75</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2079/profile_Jean_Marie_Davidson_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/87865d89b29e-davidson</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Davidson is a two-year-old little boy whose single father wishes to see him grow up healthy and strong. After being born with a cleft lip and palate, birth defects that occur when a baby’s lip and mouth do not form properly during pregnancy, Davidson had a hard time breastfeeding and taking in liquids because the fluid would pass through the opening in his mouth into his nostrils.

<p>Fortunately, Davidson was able to receive surgery to repair his lip, which is often the first half of the full course of treatment for this condition. Now he needs our help to complete the second half of his treatment, fixing his palate! The doctors expect that after this procedure, Davidson will be able to eat normally and live a healthier life.

<p>Davidson’s father is excited to see his son well again and is already making plans for the future, like sending him to school. For $960, we can help make sure Davidson has the best chance for these dreams to come true!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>235</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Teresiah</name>
   <age>47</age>
   <location>Kenya</location>
   <partner>bpQh0xZkuS</partner>
   <donors>3</donors>
   <fund_percent>12</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2120/profile_Teresiah_Magana_pre_op_pic_AMHF_Kijabe.JPG</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/ad51aac940d1-teresiah</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Teresiah is the proud mother of a 27-year-old son, who now has a family of his own. She brought him up on her own, making ends meet by selling everything from vegetables to clothes and cosmetics. 

<p>Recently, Teresiah has been experiencing pain in her abdomen and heavy menstrual cycles that leave her feeling weak. She went to the doctor’s, where they diagnosed her with fibroids.

<p>She says in Swahili, “I want to get well so that I can go back to my business and take care of myself. I do not want to be a burden to my son.” For $760, Teresiah can receive a hysterectomy to remove her uterus and the fibroids in it. 

<p>Doctors expect that  Teresiah will then be free from pain and she will feel less weak from anemia. Let’s help Teresiah to get well again so that she can put her energy back into her business ventures!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>665</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Esther</name>
   <age>1</age>
   <location>Kenya</location>
   <partner>bpQh0xZkuS</partner>
   <donors>4</donors>
   <fund_percent>12</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2227/profile_Esther_Chepterit_Logenglan_pre_op_picture1_AMHF_BKKH_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/3c4a7feda788-esther</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Esther, a five-week-old baby girl from Kenya! She is the youngest of six children and lives with her siblings and two parents.

<p>Esther was born with Spina Bifida, a congenital disorder caused by the incomplete closing of the neural tube. A portion of the spinal cords protrudes through the skin, causing an open hole in the lower back. As a result of the Spina Bifida, Esther is at risk to develop tethered cord, a condition in which the spinal cord attaches to the surrounding tissue. This can lead to mobility issues and nerve damage if it remains untreated.

<p>Esther’s mother is hopeful that Watsi can help her daughter. She says, “It has been a very difficult time for us as a family, but I am hopeful that my daughter will find treatment soon. We’ll appreciate any support for her surgery.” For $980 Esther can receive surgery to close the hole in her back. Surgery will prevent the development of tethered cord and mitigate Esther’s risk of infection. We can help her grow up to be a healthy, active child - let’s make it happen.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>860</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Phanith</name>
   <age>23</age>
   <location>Cambodia</location>
   <partner>T0R7NqdOib</partner>
   <donors>2</donors>
   <fund_percent>50</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2234/profile_Pheng_Phanith-old_website.JPG</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/ccfb1a789db2-phanith</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>23-year-old Phanith is an avid pop music fan living in Cambodia, where he works transporting farm workers across the border into Vietnam.

<p>When Phanith was young he developed an infection on his face which left him with an abcess. Surgery to remove the abcess altered the structure of his face, something which Phanith is self-conscious about.

<p>$300 will cover the cost of reconstructive surgery and will improve Phanith’s quality of life. Let’s give Phanith the boost he needs to take charge and move forward!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>150</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Maria</name>
   <age>47</age>
   <location>Guatemala</location>
   <partner>ynGZ5pnp2c</partner>
   <donors>5</donors>
   <fund_percent>12</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2235/profile_Maria_Ruiz-old_website.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/732418776736-maria</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Maria, a 47-year-old-woman from Guatemala. Several years ago, Maria developed a tumor in the roof of her mouth. The tumor has continued to grow to the point where she can not swallow and experiences severe pain.

<p>A biopsy of the tumor showed that it is benign, but the surgery to remove it is highly specialized and costly. “Maria came to us because she doesn’t know where else to turn,” Watsi’s medical partner writes. “Although she knows what treatment is necessary, she cannot afford it.”

<p>For $1,475 we can fund the full surgical procedure and care needed to remove the tumor from Maria’s mouth so that she can smile joyfully and without pain!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1295</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Thira</name>
   <age>27</age>
   <location>Cambodia</location>
   <partner>T0R7NqdOib</partner>
   <donors>0</donors>
   <fund_percent>0</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2236/profile_Hun_Thira-old_website.JPG</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/1d242b034c87-thira</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Thira is a 27-year old man living in Cambodia with his two daughters. He has been working on a fishing boat in Thailand since he was 15.

<p>One evening, while riding his motorcycle along the coast, Thira got into an accident and broke his left arm. He was unable to afford treatment in Thailand, so he sought treatment from his village healer in Cambodia. Unfortunately, the treatment was unsuccessful and now Thira is unable to use his arm.

<p>$300 will cover the costs of a surgery to align the bone in his arm. Your donation will restore function in Thira’s left arm and reduce his pain.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>300</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Sok Nai</name>
   <age>5</age>
   <location>Cambodia</location>
   <partner>T0R7NqdOib</partner>
   <donors>0</donors>
   <fund_percent>0</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2237/profile_Ny-33537.pre_op-03_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/581598d4a88d-sok-nai</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Say hello to Sok Nai from Cambodia, an adorable five-year-old boy who loves playing with his friends and three siblings.

<p>At one-year-old, Sok Nai was badly burned by a cooking fire. He now experiences trouble moving his hands and legs as his burn scars continue to thicken. The doctors from our medical partner, Children’s Surgical Centre, can perform contracture release surgery and skin grafts to improve Sok Nai’s function.

<p>$300 will cover the costs of Sok Nai’s procedure. Your donation will restore function and mobility to his hands and arms. Let’s make sure this five-year-old has every chance to keep playing as actively as possible!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>300</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>San Thwin</name>
   <age>40</age>
   <location>Burma</location>
   <partner>WgpdmY5ITB</partner>
   <donors>0</donors>
   <fund_percent>0</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2238/profile_BWMF_Daw_San_San_Thwin_F40_Myoma_PreOp__2__.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/2fb793b9bae5-san-thwin</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>A farmer by trade, San Thwin works side by side her husband tilling land on farms in Hway Shan, Burma. 

<p>San Thwin is known by her friends for her inner strength. She lost her father at a young age, and after his passing, stayed home to help her mother support the family instead of going to school. She never learned to read or write.

<p>In March of this year, San Thwin noticed the first symptoms of a myoma, a benign tumor that grows within the muscle tissue of the uterus. She lost her appetite, developed abdominal pain, and when lying down she felt a small mass in her abdomen. San Thwin sought advice from her community’s healer and midwife who initially believed her to be pregnant. However, after further examination at a clinic, she was diagnosed with a myoma. San Thwin continued to help her husband with farm work until her pain became too severe. Now they can no longer cover the cost of their living or medical treatments. Sam Thwin deeply wants to get better so she can return to her livelihood.

<p>For $865, San Thwin will have an operation that surgically removes the myoma gyn condition 2 from her abdomen. After receiving treatment, she will no longer experience chronic pain and can return to her normal life with her husband. Lets help her achieve this!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>865</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Ma Linn</name>
   <age>36</age>
   <location>Burma</location>
   <partner>WgpdmY5ITB</partner>
   <donors>0</donors>
   <fund_percent>0</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2239/profile_BWMF_Ma_Kyi_Linn_F36_Myoma_PreOp__2__.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/04016bb8c59b-ma-linn</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Ma Linn is a 36-year-old mother from Burma. She started to notice pain in her abdomen after she delivered her youngest child three years ago. Her doctor told her she had a small mass growing in her uterus that needed to be removed as soon as possible, but Ma Linn didn’t have enough money to pay for the surgery. The mass continued to grow and she experienced pain more and more frequently. Now, she has been diagnosed with uterine fibroids and cysts in both of her ovaries.

<p>Ma Linn used to work with her husband as an agricultural day laborer. Ma Linn and her husband support their six children (3 boys and 3 girls) and her mother. Three of her children attend school, which adds to their expenses. Right now, her husband is the only one looking after their children and earning an income because Ma Linn is too weak and in too much pain to help. Ma Linn hopes to get treatment soon so that she can return to her home in Burma. She cannot wait to be healthy enough to take care of her family and their crops and not worry about the pain she experiences on a daily basis.

<p>Ma Linn needs surgery to remove the uterine fibroids and cysts, preventing further growth and easing her pain. With our help, she can focus on what matters in her life.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1500</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Eva</name>
   <age>37</age>
   <location>Guatemala</location>
   <partner>ynGZ5pnp2c</partner>
   <donors>0</donors>
   <fund_percent>0</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2244/profile_foto_26-05-14_Eva_Adelina__Por_Con_522_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/ca487bac7fd8-eva</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Eva, a 37-year-old from Guatemala. Eva works in a local market as a saleswoman. She has severe arthritis that causes significant and constant pain, especially in her hands and knees. She cannot perform her normal tasks around the home. Her income has suffered as she finds it hard to sell her goods in the market like she used to. Because this issue has been so long standing, she is also battling depression.

<p>Eva was receiving treatment for her condition and felt much improved. However, she subsequently ran out of money and had to end treatment. Her family is very supportive but cannot afford to continue her care. She’s come to our medical partner, ynGZ5pnp2c, looking for help to get her treatment back on track.

<p>For $450, her treatment will be resumed. She will get started on immune suppressing medications to modulate her inflammation and get her arthritis under control. Doctors will monitor for any side effects from these medications extensively and adjust the treatment as necessary. They anticipate that the treatment will be highly effective and that she will be pain free and able to get back to her life! Let’s make it happen!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>450</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Eunice</name>
   <age>25</age>
   <location>Kenya</location>
   <partner>bi3MUrEJER</partner>
   <donors>6</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2229/profile_Eunice_Akinyi_Ochieng_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/50a79cc5d938-eunice</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>25-year-old Eunice is a happy, loving mother of three with another child on the way. Eunice and her family live in Kenya, where she works as a businesswoman selling vegetables at the nearby local market to sustain the family. Her husband is a farmer and grows maize, beans, millet, cassavas and vegetables for the family and sells some crops when the harvest is in surplus to pay school fees for their children.

<p>As Eunice and her husband work very hard to provide for their beautiful family and ensure their children receive a good education, they cannot save money and pay the required amount for the delivery of their child in a healthcare facility. In the later stages of her pregnancy she has come to feel chronically fatigued accompanied by dizziness, which is so acute she is unable to perform daily household chores. For Eunice this is especially difficult, as she always feels that everything is impossible until it’s done and according to her, she cannot believe that one day she will deliver safely in the hands of qualified birth attendants due to her inability to afford the cost of medical care.

<p>$215 is all Eunice needs to ensure she will undergo the delivery in a health facility, under the care of competent nurses where she will receive medical advice and regular follow-ups with the help of Maternal Child Health Workers. Let’s give Eunice and her baby the excellent care they deserve as Eunice, her husband and children welcome another member of their family!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>215</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Balika</name>
   <age>8</age>
   <location>Nepal</location>
   <partner>Possible</partner>
   <donors>11</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2233/profile_Balika_Nath-old_website.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/f475fa69e521-balika</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Eight-year-old Balika is from Nepal, is in 2nd class, and loves skipping. She lives with her extended family, a total of 11 members. Balika’s father and uncle work in India most of the year to support the family. During the four-month monsoon season they come home to plant rice on their land.

<p>15 days ago, Balika pricked her finger while collecting fodder in the forest. The following day her cut became red and tender. Her mother applied local herbs to speed up the healing process but the infection continued and spread up her hand. “Without treatment, this infection can lead to necrosis or gangrene, which can cause scarring, deformity, or at worst amputation,” our medical partner writes.

<p>It will cost $215 to drain the abscess on Balika’s left middle finger and care for the wound with antibiotics. Your donation will give Balika appropriate care to ensure that her finger is okay so she continue to go to school and play without further worry.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>215</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Thi Aye</name>
   <age>18</age>
   <location>Burma</location>
   <partner>WgpdmY5ITB</partner>
   <donors>13</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2158/profile_BAMF_Thidar_Aye_F18_Hemangioma_PreOp__2__.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/f68e053ecc06-thi-aye</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Thi Aye is a skillful 18-year-old young woman from Burma who has been living with a hemangioma in her left cheek her entire life. Hemangioma is a benign tumor, though it can become enlarged over time and causes pain, discomfort, and emotional side effects.

<p>As the years went by, the hemangioma began to interfere with her eating, as she would bite the growth on her left cheek when chewing her food. When she was 14, Thi Aye dropped out of school and started delivering vegetables at the market to help support her family. At work and in the evening she felt a painful tightness in her mouth, and she would have severe headaches about once a week. She carried the vegetables in a large basket on her head, but after a few months of working the basket’s weight began to put pressure on the hemangioma, causing her severe discomfort.

<p>Her condition made it impossible to continue selling vegetables, though Thi Aye was determined to continue to work. Five months ago she began working at home sewing clothing until her family’s home burned down in December 2013. She now lives under the shelter of a tree with eight other family members while her father builds a new home in a new village.

<p>Thi Aye has undergone surgery twice for her condition around the age of 16, though both surgeries failed to completely remove the hemangioma. Thi Aye is now seeking permanent surgical removal of her tumor, which will free her of pain and give her a fresh start. Thi Aye is very eager to work again and looks forward to undergoing treatment so she can regain her confidence and find a new job that she enjoys. For $1500 we can help Thi Aye to live pain-free so she can focus on finding her passion!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1500</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Douglas</name>
   <age>1</age>
   <location>Guatemala</location>
   <partner>ynGZ5pnp2c</partner>
   <donors>12</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2178/profile_foto_05-06-14_Duglas_Mendez_7704_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/18349fdc7874-douglas</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet one-year-old Douglas from Guatemala. Douglas’ family is struggling to keep food on the table. This has contributed to Douglas’ medical problems, which includes severe malnutrition. They are happy to have finally connected with a source of medical help and are hoping to see a positive change soon.

<p>Douglas was referred to our partner clinic in Guatemala because of malnutrition. He is chronically ill with intestinal infections. As a result, Douglas has a poor appetite and low energy levels. Believe it or not, he has not gained any weight at all in almost a year. He has also not grown in height and is not walking and talking like a normal 1.5 year old.

<p>We’re raising $525 for Douglas’ intensive nutritional therapy. Without our help, his growth will remain stunted in many ways, physically and mentally. But with your support, we can ensure that his chronic intestinal infections are cured, that he resumes growth, and that his developmental progress will pick up.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>525</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Iyanna</name>
   <age>1</age>
   <location>Tanzania</location>
   <partner>bpQh0xZkuS</partner>
   <donors>8</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2114/profile_Iyanna_Innocent_Preop_Pic_AMHF_ALMC_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/32959e5ceb75-iyanna</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Iyanna is a happy one-year-old who likes to be around people. She is her parents’ first child.

<p>Parts of Iyanna’s intestinal tract do not function. She has had a colostomy, an operation that provides an alternative channel for feces to leave her body. Iyanna has had complications with her colostomy, with bleeding and the risk of infection. She needs a further operation to close her colostomy and make her intestines work normally.

<p>Iyanna’s parents both work hard in the village market in Tanzania. Her mother says, “It is a blessing to have a child. Our prayer is to see our baby able to use the bathroom like any other normal person and be able to go to school and become independent”. The surgery Iyanna needs costs $1200, and it will give Iyanna a healthy, normal childhood, free from medical complications. Let’s give Iyanna, and her loving parents, that gift.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1200</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Purity</name>
   <age>1</age>
   <location>Kenya</location>
   <partner>bpQh0xZkuS</partner>
   <donors>14</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2048/profile_Purity_Sarah_Okumo_pre_op_picture2_AMHF_BKKH.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/cac0fefb13b0-purity</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Purity is a seven-month-old girl from Kenya. She was the last born child in a family of five children. Her father is a casual laborer, and her mother is a housewife. Purity’s family owns a small piece of land where they do small scale farming for the family’s needs.

<p>Purity lives with hydrocephalus, a lethal condition which causes her head to become enlarged and increases the pressure within her skull. Purity’s mother says, “I was shocked to see my child’s head size grow day by day. I pray that she will be treated soon, and I request for help.”

<p>To relieve the pressure and save her life, Purity needs a shunt incision. If the surgery is not done, Purity is likely to suffer brain damage due to the increased intra-cranial pressure.

<p>For $980, we fund this procedure which will relieve the pressure in her head. Let’s help Purity live a normal childhood without the pain she’s experiencing now!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>980</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Petcy</name>
   <age>1</age>
   <location>Kenya</location>
   <partner>bpQh0xZkuS</partner>
   <donors>15</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2030/profile_Petcy_Jepkorir_Cherogonyio_pre_op_picture1_AMHF_BKKH.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/ddf16a6694ea-petcy</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Petcy, a-one-year-old from Kenya. Petcy is the youngest of four children. Her parents lease a piece of land that they farm to support the family. They live in a rented house in a town nearby the farm.

<p>Petcy lives with spina bifida, a condition in which a portion of the spinal cord protrudes outside the back. Petcy needs surgery on her back to remedy this, otherwise she is in danger of developing an infection and various back problems like tethered cord, kyphosis and scoliosis.

<p>Petcy’s mother is worried but optimistic. She says, “The birth of my daughter was a happy moment for me but when I was told that she would need surgery on her back, I felt as though my happiness was being taken away because we cannot pay for her treatment. I pray that Petcy gets treated and recovers so that she can have a good future.”

<p>For $980, surgery will be performed that will answer that prayer! The surgery will allow Petcy to live a normal life. Let’s make it happen!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>980</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Daw Tin</name>
   <age>54</age>
   <location>Burma</location>
   <partner>WgpdmY5ITB</partner>
   <donors>8</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2200/profile_Daw_Tin_Yee-resized.JPG</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/68383f1cf53f-daw-tin</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Daw Tin! Daw Tin is a 54-year-old mother of five and lives in Burma with her family. Daw Tin and her husband work on their family farm with the help of their sons.

<p>Daw Tin has had a prolapsed uterus for the last eight years. Some of her symptoms, including pain in her uterus and extreme dizziness, keep her from being able to eat and sleep well. Daw Tin is also unable to carry out her daily chores or help on the family farm, which impacts the family financially.

<p>By surgically removing her uterus, doctors will be able to provide Daw Tin with the opportunity to be free from the daily pain which she has experienced for so long. Help us raise $1150 to keep Daw Tin healthy so she can be free of stress and join her husband in work on the farm.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1150</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Habiba</name>
   <age>11</age>
   <location>Tanzania</location>
   <partner>bpQh0xZkuS</partner>
   <donors>8</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2124/profile_Habiba_Ibrahim_Preop_Pic_1__AMHF_ALMC.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/f5e2ae91bc7b-habiba</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Habiba is a studious 11-year-old girl who enjoys history, geography, languages and playing netball. She says, “My dream is to become a doctor when I grow up”.

<p>Habiba was born with Hirschprung’s disease, where parts of the intestine do not function. She does not pass stool normally. She recently experienced severe abdominal pains with fevers. She was diagnosed with enterocolitis, an inflammation of the intestine, which will kill her if not treated.

<p>Habiba’s parents are both primary school teachers, and they have three children. They have taken Habiba to several hospitals without improvement, spending all their savings, hoping to cure her. The life-saving surgery Habiba needs costs $1200 but her loving parents cannot afford it. After the surgery she will be able to pass stool normally.

<p>Your donation will get Habiba the operation she needs to free her from her life-threatening condition and get her back to school healthy. Let’s make it possible for Habiba to follow her dream of becoming a doctor one day!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1200</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Lilian</name>
   <age>1</age>
   <location>Guatemala</location>
   <partner>ynGZ5pnp2c</partner>
   <donors>15</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2196/profile_LillianProfile.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/9e7985c0d510-lilian</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Lillian is a one-year-old baby from Guatemala who comes from a family with limited resources. Due to an ongoing illness and because food is often scarce in her home, Lillian has not been getting the nutrition she needs to grow as she should. She is extremely underweight and short for her age and her development is not progressing much month to month. She can’t sit or speak, and has limited energy. 

<p>For $525, our medical partner, ynGZ5pnp2c, can provide intensive nutritional therapy that will help Lillian develop normally again. 

<p>Her doctor notes that Lillian’s family are attentive to her condition and are “looking forward to working with us to turn around their child’s health.” Let’s help give Lillian a chance at a healthy life!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>525</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Maria</name>
   <age>32</age>
   <location>Guatemala</location>
   <partner>ynGZ5pnp2c</partner>
   <donors>12</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2176/profile_20140407_121703_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/e8dfca477c10-maria</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Maria is a 32-year-old woman who lives in Guatemala. She has a rare condition called mixed connective tissue disorder. This condition has caused extreme tightening of her skin, making it difficult for Maria to bend her hands and elbows. She also experiences severe pain and swelling in all of her joints, limiting her ability to work around the house. The chronic cough and fatigue with exercise which Maria has developed is also concerning for both her heart and lungs.

<p>“Maria has been looking for help for her condition for years,” her doctor writes. “She has seen dozens of doctors but no one has been able to figure out what is going on. Fortunately, we immediately knew what condition she had when we met her (it is a very rare condition!) and we are excited to work with her to make steps toward controlling her disease.”

<p>Care for Maria’s condition will include evaluation of her heart and lung function as well as immunosuppressive medications to control her pain and stiffness, improve her quality of life and ability to handle day-to-day tasks as well as limit further organ damage.

<p>Maria has finally found the specialty care which she needs to control her disease. With $1100, we can make sure that she gets it.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1100</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Sok Khom</name>
   <age>36</age>
   <location>Cambodia</location>
   <partner>T0R7NqdOib</partner>
   <donors>11</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2161/profile_Ou_Sok_Khom_Pre_Op_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/9225320297cf-sok-khom</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Sok Khom is a father of three and a policeman in Cambodia. Last November, Sok Khom broke his leg in a motorbike accident during a major national festival. He was hospitalized for almost a month and spent all of his savings paying the medical bill.

<p>However, Sok Khom’s fracture did not heal well. He now feels pain when he puts weight on his leg. A surgery to correct his bone alignment costs $300, but Sok Khom has no savings left to pay for this care.

<p>Let’s get the $300 Sok Khom needs to make his leg straight and strong again. Your donation will free him from pain, and restore his mobility, which is so important to his job as a policeman!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>300</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Stephania</name>
   <age>3</age>
   <location>Tanzania</location>
   <partner>bpQh0xZkuS</partner>
   <donors>9</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2063/profile_Sephania_600x352.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/23248e04a7d5-stephania</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Stephania, a three-year-old who can light up any room with her big brown eyes. She lives in Tanzania with her parents, older sister, and her favorite teddy bear which she carries around everywhere and even sleeps with—they’re inseparable! Her parents work hard to care for their family, especially for their youngest daughter. Her mother says, “It was a bit difficult for my husband to accept Stephania because he badly wanted to have a baby boy after getting a baby girl,” but she explains that “as time went by he has come to love her so much.”

<p>Stephania has Hirschsprung’s disease, a condition that causes her to have constant stomachaches and makes passing stool without the help of bowel irrigation impossible. Her mother, a hotel waitress, and her father, a sales clerk at an electronics store, have spent their savings taking Stephania to the hospital for years. Now, they are unable to afford her surgery.

<p>An abdominoperineal pull through and colostomy closure will cost $1,200 and allow Stephania to eat freely and have healthy bowel movements. Her mother says, “all we need is for our baby to be healthy, as happy as her sister, and be able to go to school.” Let’s help Stephania get treatment so she can wear a big smile on her first day of school!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1200</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Everlyne</name>
   <age>19</age>
   <location>Kenya</location>
   <partner>bi3MUrEJER</partner>
   <donors>6</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2217/profile_Everlyne_Awuor_Oyugi__.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/8b5e1bbf71f3-everlyne</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Everlyne is a 19-year-old mother of one who lives with her husband and child in Kenya. Everlyne’s husband, a farmer, grows maize, beans, and vegetables and sells some of the produce to support the basic needs of his family.

<p>Everlyne is pregnant with her second child but in the evening is experiencing abdominal pain and back pains, which interrupts her activities. “I pray for a safe delivery in a health facility and also that one day, we will invest in better farming. After a safe delivery, I would wish to start family planning,” says Everlyne.

<p>For $215, we can give Everlyne a safe delivery in a health facility attended to by a skilled clinician. Everlyne will receive regular check-ups and medical services when necessary and will be able to carry on with her duties as usual after a successful delivery. Let’s support Everlyne and her family as they welcome a new baby!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>215</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Julius</name>
   <age>1</age>
   <location>Tanzania</location>
   <partner>bpQh0xZkuS</partner>
   <donors>9</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2083/profile_Julius_Parmiria_Preop_Pic_1__AMHF_ALMC_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/b2932c812a4c-julius</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Julius, a newborn living in Tanzania! Julius was born with an open myelomenigocele with hydrocephalus. This means that Julius is leaking cerebral spinal fluid from his back. This condition is lethal. If left untreated, he will develop sepsis and become dehydrated.

<p>Julius was born during a rainstorm. His parents were unable to arrange transportation to the hospital for days after his birth. They are cattle farmers who support their two children as well as their extended family, and therefore cannot afford Julius’ operation.

<p>His parents say, “Julius is our answered prayer. After getting a baby girl, we prayed for a baby boy and the Lord blessed us with one. It is our prayer that he will survive and grow up like other children and later on be helpful to us and the society at large.”

<p>$1025 will pay for a myelomenigocele closure and a ventriculoperitoneal shunt insertion. This will cause the cerebral spinal fluid to stop leaking and allow Julius to learn how to sit up. Help us allow Julius to continue learning and growing!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1025</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Josefa</name>
   <age>43</age>
   <location>Guatemala</location>
   <partner>ynGZ5pnp2c</partner>
   <donors>6</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2175/profile_JosefaCalel10032_foto1_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/f7a9048dedab-josefa</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Josefa is a 43-year-old woman who lives in Guatemala. For the last six months, she has been experiencing severe dermatitis. Because of this, Josefa has huge ulcerations, or breaks in her skin, as well as large scaling on both of her legs.

<p>The itchiness and pain keeps Josefa up at night, and topical ointments and medications aren’t helping. With further medical care, including a 6-12 month course of immunosuppressive medication under close monitoring, Josefa should be able to see marked improvement in her symptoms.

<p>“Josefa is a great woman who has put up with this condition for six months with a smile on her face,” our hospital partner writes. “However, it is starting to take its toll. She is exhausted and at her wit’s end. She needs our help to get this condition behind her.”

<p>With $500 we can cover the cost of Josefa’s medication, lab testing and monitoring as well as the cost of transportation associated with care. Let’s help Josefa get the relief she needs.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>500</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Hilda</name>
   <age>26</age>
   <location>Kenya</location>
   <partner>bi3MUrEJER</partner>
   <donors>4</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2185/profile_Hilda_Achieng_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/d3bea7514084-hilda</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Hilda is a 26-year-old wife and mother of three children who lives with her family in Kenya. Her husband works as a sugarcane miller, but hopes to find another job to better support the family.

<p>Hilda is expecting her fourth child and is experiencing abdominal pain and severe headaches associated with her pregnancy. As she prepares to welcome her newborn into this world, Hilda fears that a home delivery would expose both mom and baby to germs and putting both lives in danger. She worries about not being able to pay for a safe delivery.

<p>With $215 let’s ease Hilda’s worry and provide her a venue to deliver her baby safely, especially in the event of complication, as well as postpartum care.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>215</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Maung Aung</name>
   <age>4</age>
   <location>Thailand</location>
   <partner>WgpdmY5ITB</partner>
   <donors>15</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2157/profile_BCMF_Maung_Aung_Thein_M4_Burns_PreOp__6__.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/867f14c5b6e7-maung-aung</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Though he is only four, Maung has already set some impressive goals for himself: he already knows that he wants to be a doctor when he grows up!

<p>Maung Aung’s journey to connecting with Watsi began five months ago. He woke up in the middle of the night needing to use the bathroom. His house does not have electricity, so he took a candle with him. The candle slipped, and his pajamas caught fire. Maung Aung suffered burns down his face and body which have turned into stiff, rubbery keloid scars over time.

<p>Maung Aung is an active kid. Since the accident, he’s often frustrated by his lack of full movement in his arm. He also has trouble walking because the skin on his right leg has contracted, causing him a lot of pain when he moves it.

<p>For $1500, we can help Maung Aung receive plastic surgery to remove the scarred skin and improve movement in his right arm and right leg. With treatment, he has a better chance of starting school next year and learning to look after himself like normal kids as he grows up. He says what he looks forward to most is playing with his friends.

<p>Let’s help this inspiring boy get well so he can attend school and live a normal, healthy life!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1500</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Su Wai</name>
   <age>32</age>
   <location>Burma</location>
   <partner>WgpdmY5ITB</partner>
   <donors>8</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2155/profile_BWMF_Su_Wai_Phyo_F32_Mutiple_Ovary_Cyst_PreOp__3__.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/2c1555509991-su-wai</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Su Wai is 32-years-old and lives with her husband in Burma. Her husband works as a motorcycle taxi-driver. They recently got married and want to have children one day.

<p>Due to multiple cysts in her ovaries, Su Wai experiences severe pain in her abdomen and finds it difficult to move or do house chores. The daily pain that Su Wai experiences has caused her to stop working. The couple now depend solely on her husbands income.

<p>Su Wai needs an operation to have her cysts removed. She looks forward to being able to take care of her home again and get back to work so she and her husband can be more financially secure. Although her doctor cannot tell her for sure whether she can have a child after the operation, she remains hopeful. The couple dream of having a family.

<p>The operation she needs costs $1150. Your donation will enable Su Wai to overcome this condition and start building a happy future with her husband!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1150</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Juana</name>
   <age>6</age>
   <location>Guatemala</location>
   <partner>ynGZ5pnp2c</partner>
   <donors>15</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2174/profile_JuanaZapeta13615_foto3_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/4b87b72ef48d-juana</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Juana is a 6-year-old girl who lives in Guatemala with her mother, a single parent. She has Down’s syndrome and, like many children with this condition, she also suffers from congenital heart disease.

<p>Juana has a type of heart disease called a ventricular septal defect. The defect will need to be repaired surgically to prevent heart failure. Before her heart can be repaired, Juana will need a little dental work to prevent serious infection during her surgery. Once both the dental work and heart surgery are completed, Juana will have a well-functioning heart for years to come.

<p>With $1475, we can give Juana a shot at living a healthy, happy life with her mother. Let’s do it.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1475</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Zin Zin</name>
   <age>16</age>
   <location>Burma</location>
   <partner>WgpdmY5ITB</partner>
   <donors>11</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2154/profile_BCMF_Zin_Zin_Mu_F16y_NHL_PreOpt__6__.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/e5c7a94d65e1-zin-zin</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet 16-year-old Zin Zin from Burma. Zin Zin is a bright young student with dreams of becoming an engineer. She lives with her parents, two sisters and grandmother.

<p>Last year, Zin Zin had to put her schooling on hold after she was diagnosed with Non-Hodgkin lymphoma of the nasal cavity. The lymphoma in her nasal cavity spread into her eye cavity causing her eye to become displaced. Zin Zin says she is not experiencing pain, but her bulging right eye has made her self-conscious. As the tumor continues to grow, Zin Zin ha started losing her eyesight. 

<p>Although Zin Zin’s father works hard as a porter at a train station, he earns just enough to cover the family’s day-to-day needs and cannot support the extra expense of surgery. For $1500, doctors can remove the tumor in her nasal cavity and the detached damaged eye. Let’s help Zin Zin get healthy so she can return to school and pursue her dreams of becoming an engineer!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1500</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Sokeo</name>
   <age>2</age>
   <location>Cambodia</location>
   <partner>T0R7NqdOib</partner>
   <donors>6</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2166/profile_Kuo-28167_lala_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/dc772c1a0fef-sokeo</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Sokeo is a two-year-old boy who likes playing with cars and other toys. Like most toddlers his age, he is also getting used to exploring the world on his two feet and honing his quickly developing motor skills.

<p>When Sokeo was a newborn, he developed a high fever which was treated with injections to his thighs. As a result of those injections, he developed fibrosis (thickening and scarring) of his quadricep muscles which has led to muscle contractures that limit the flexion of his knees. In April, our medical partners at Children’s Surgical Centre performed surgery on his right knee to release the contracture and increase mobility. Now, he needs the same surgery and physical therapy for his left knee.

<p>For only $225, we can help Sokeo complete the final stage of treatment which will increase his functioning and mobility and decrease pain. Let’s make sure this little guy has every chance to be as rambunctious a toddler as he should be!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>225</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Che</name>
   <age>2</age>
   <location>Cambodia</location>
   <partner>T0R7NqdOib</partner>
   <donors>3</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2162/profile_33195_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/48cf5ae8c01d-che</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>This little two-year-old, sitting cozily on her dads hip, is named Che. Che loves her family and especially likes to play with her sister.

<p>When Che was seven months old, cooking gas exploded in her home and she was severely burnt in several places, including her face and hands. Her parents took her to a local clinic where she was treated with skin grafts. However, the burns were so severe that when the grafts healed, the scar tissue was thick. This thick scar tissue is now contracted, and it prevents Che from using her hands normally.

<p>Che needs a $300 surgery to release the contracted scar tissue. It will ensure that she can participate in more activities, like hand writing, as she grows up. Let’s make sure Che gets this surgery so she can enjoy full movement in her hands!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>300</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Nancy</name>
   <age>16</age>
   <location>Kenya</location>
   <partner>AbehswjNUa</partner>
   <donors>5</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2153/profile_Kenya_Nancy-Chebet_X_LS-600x479_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/77ba9f6a5181-nancy</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Nancy, a 16-year-old girl from Kenya. For the past nine months, Nancy has lived with a soft tissue mass on her left hand.

<p>Nancy graduated from primary school last year and just entered high school. This can be a difficult transition for any teenager, but Nancy’s condition makes her especially self-conscious. She has tried to hide the mass to avoid embarrassment. The swelling also limits Nancy’s ability to use her hand and causes discomfort.

<p>Nancy will go through a biopsy during her stay at Watsi medical partner, AbehswjNUa. Based on the results of the biopsy, doctors will be able to decide on what the best form of treatment will be for her. Nancy says, “I feel this hand has denied me good health. I want good health back.” Let’s help Nancy so that she can focus more on school and friends!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1000</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Reaksa</name>
   <age>5</age>
   <location>Cambodia</location>
   <partner>T0R7NqdOib</partner>
   <donors>2</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2164/profile_Thin_Reaksa_Pre_Op_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/6f5562639714-reaksa</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Say hello to Reaksa! She is a sweet five-year-old girl who lives in Cambodia.

<p>Two months ago, Reaksa broke her leg in a motorbike accident. She was given a bamboo cast in her village, resulting in a malunion of her tibia. This means her fracture healed in a position that affects the mechanical function of her leg. Walking is often painful and difficult for Reaksa.

<p>Reaksa wants to walk the way she did before the accident. Let’s raise $300 and give Reaksa an ORIF osteotomy, a treatment that will shift the weight away from the damaged cartilage to an area with healthier cartilage, improving her mobility. Let’s help Reaksa get back on her feet!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>300</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Juvensio</name>
   <age>1</age>
   <location>Zambia</location>
   <partner>AbehswjNUa</partner>
   <donors>20</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2128/profile_Zambia_Juvensio_WatsiCover_.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/9fd04277984a-juvensio</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Juvensio is an energetic one-year-old who lives with his mother in Zambia. He was born with spina bifida, a dangerous condition which leaves the spine protruding in a fluid filled sack on his back, which makes Juvensio susceptible to infection and spinal cord damage.

<p>Bernadette, Juvensio’s mom, is certain that her baby boy is going to be a great man some day. Even when family and friends suggested she abandon Juvensio, Bernadette stood up to them. The benefits of addressing Juvensio’s condition are promising, he would be less susceptible to infection, spinal damage, and no longer be at risk of fatality. The cost of the procedure, called a meningocele repair, is out of reach for Juvensio and his mother.

<p>With $2000 we can help Juvensio move on with his life. We can give him the opportunity to make his loving mother’s dreams for him come true: to become a great man.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>2000</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Woodley</name>
   <age>2</age>
   <location>Haiti</location>
   <partner>Y5GlFHGFuO</partner>
   <donors>3</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2090/profile_IMG_0144.JPG</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/099af67feb13-woodley</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Woodley! Woodley is a two-year-old boy from Haiti who lives with his mom and sister. Woodley’s mom is a street vendor, selling second-hand clothes.

<p>Recently, Woodley arrived at the hospital with severe difficulty breathing because of a large mass on his neck that was pressing on his trachea. Doctors performed an emergency procedure and placed a tube in his neck to help him breathe. Woodley received this procedure just in time. If his mom had waited any longer to bring him in, doctors say he would have died.

<p>Woodley now needs surgery to remove the mass in his neck, which doctors think was caused by an infection. For $1,000, Woodley will receive this surgery that will allow him to breathe on his own. Woodley’s mom says that once Woodley is better again, she would like to send him to school. Let’s help Woodley breathe normally again and get him to school!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>1000</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Oloisoloi</name>
   <age>15</age>
   <location>Tanzania</location>
   <partner>bpQh0xZkuS</partner>
   <donors>2</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/1989/profile_Oloisoloi_Saitabau_Preop_Pic_1__AMHF_ALMC.jpg</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/f855839094d9-oloisoloi</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Oloisoloi, a 15-year-old boy from Tanzania. He started his primary education when he was 11 and is now in 4th grade. He plans on becoming a doctor.

<p>Oloisoloi was born with a congenital condition where his right leg did not full develop. Until recently, he’d been successfully getting around thanks to a prosthesis. Now, his tibia has grown and is protruding and he can no longer use that prosthesis. Because he hasn’t been able to walk around, Oloisoloi has had to miss a lot of school. Oloisoloi’s parents cannot afford to pay for an operation or to buy a new prosthetic leg for their son.

<p>For $800, Oloisoloi will receive a new prosthesis and have his tibia refashioned to fit it. Doctors expect that this new prosthesis will be comfortable to use, since he outgrew his old prosthesis. Let’s help Oloisoloi walk around easily again, so that he can return to school and pursue his wish to become a doctor!
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>800</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patient_info>
   <name>Lalanne</name>
   <age>1</age>
   <location>Haiti</location>
   <partner>Y5GlFHGFuO</partner>
   <donors>16</donors>
   <fund_percent>100</fund_percent>
   <profile_img>https://d3w52z135jkm97.cloudfront.net/uploads/profile/image/2051/profile_Lalanne_Cheldley.JPG</profile_img>
   <profile_link>https://watsi.org/profile/09b83b46c66b-lalanne</profile_link>
   <medical_desc><div class="span8"><p>Meet Lalanne, a one-year-old girl living in Haiti. Born with a cleft palate, Lalanne has difficulties eating and drinking. For a growing kid, this poses major development problems.

<p>Lalanne’s mother is from the Haitian countryside, and provides for her three children on her own. She is determined to take care of her family and wants to make life good for Lalanne, but she’s already done all she can afford to help her daughter overcome this condition and grow up healthy.

<p>Lalanne already underwent one round of repair surgery, but needs one more procedure to fix her cleft palate so she can use her lips correctly. For $960, we can make the simple, daily tasks of eating and drinking better for Lalanne.
</medical_desc>
   <to_raise>960</to_raise>
</patient_info>
<patients>